Chapter 1190: Encirclement

Numerous powerful conscients gathered within a secret space, their powerful auras forming huge black silhouettes. There were a few new figures amongst them, containing unfathomable power.

*Rumble!* Space split apart at that moment, and the powers of the world and original sin entered the space.

“Everyone!” Leylin fashioned a form out of original sin, looking at the silhouettes around him. Every person here was a peak rank 8 existence!

“The gods have stabilised their divine kingdoms, interfering with our actions in the prime material plane. Even as the world combination project was underway, someone divulged our current situation.”

“Keke.. So you’re saying there’s a traitor amongst us?” Another voice Leylin was familiar with sounded, carrying obvious hostility.

“Of course, Distorted Shadow. Furthermore, it could even be you!” Leylin stared fearlessly at the peak rank 8 Magus, exchanging thoughts rapidly.

“I can swear upon my truesoul that I never revealed any information about the plan…” Distorted Shadow looked coldly at Leylin. “Instead, Lord of Original Sin, why did you not devour the entire prime material plane and destroy the gods in one fell swoop? You seem quite suspicious!”

“The sun is one thing, but the prime material plane is a whole other matter. It’s the foundation of the World of Gods, the base of all existence. Destroying it would be like destroying the World of Gods itself, not something a peak rank 8 can do.” Mother Core stood up for her ally.

“I feel like the gods have begun their counterattack, and they definitely won’t miss the opportunity. Please wait and see, everyone!” Leylin glared coldly at Distorted Shadow, his indifference causing the other party to feel apprehensive.

“All we can do right now is to speed up the two-world plan…” an existence surrounded by darkness spoke up, every word seemingly coming from a deep abyss. This was the Darkness Lord, a peak rank 8 existence from the Dark World.

“Our true bodies are currently outside the crystal sphere, and we can’t easily dispatch them…” another figure spoke, radiating the green light of life. This was the ancient Tree of Life, a huge tree from the Life World that had harnessed the power of magic.

However, even as the numerous peak rank 8s were discussing the issue, a rumble sounded from the depths of the Abyss, as if to verify Leylin’s words. A sort of sacred natural radiance sealed off the entire Abyss, numerous golden silhouettes walking out to the hymns of their followers.

“The gods! They’re taking action with their true bodies!” Mother Core waved her hands, displaying a huge image that allowed those present to see the gods’ lineup.

“Tyr, Tempus, Talos, Oghma, and Gruumsh… All of them are powerful gods, the Chaos Lord and Evil Filthy Eye are in danger!”

Leylin looked around his surroundings, unable to find the conscients of those two existences. As chaotic existences themselves, they grew intoxicated with the pleasure of plundering the Abyss and lost all interest in the outside world. They didn’t realise the crisis they were in.

“Keke… It’s rare for such strong existences to be willing to step out of their divine kingdoms…” The Darkness Lord sneered. “If we push the two-world plan back and move out together, at least half of them will fall.”

Peak rank 8 Magi were equivalent to greater gods within the World of Gods. The difference was that their powers belonged to them alone, so in a fight outside of the divine kingdoms the Magi would definitely win. One had to agree that Darkness Lord’s suggestion was enticing, causing a few Magi to stir.

“I wouldn’t do that if I were you…” Leylin stood out at that moment, speaking coldly.

“Substantiate. Why? It’s not easy to find a chance to eliminate so many powerful gods in one fell swoop…” As expected, Distorted Shadow jumped out immediately, speaking with ulterior motives.

“Haven’t you all realized that the most powerful existences within God’s World have yet to appear?” Leylin glanced at Distorted Shadow, his voice was full of disdain.

There were differences even amongst powerful gods. Oghma, for example, couldn’t match Tempus the God of Fighting in combat.

Past rank 18, there were a few gods who were known for their combat. The four elemental gods were an example. Akadi, Grumbar, Istishia and Kossuth were all ancient gods, staying within their elemental planes of wind, earth, water, and fire respectively. They stood aloof from worldly affairs, holding secrets even most gods didn’t know in their arsenal.

There were also gods like Ubtao, Silvanus, Jergal, and Chauntea. They were formidable beings, powerful enough to be the monarchs of their own worlds, second only to the Overgod himself. That these powerful gods had yet to appear in the Abyss caused Leylin to grow vigilant.

……

“Oh? You’re here in your true bodies? Were you ordered to abandon your mouse holes and come to the Abyss?” Azure power had converged above what was once the Argent Palace in Azzagrat, forming a many-eyed giant with a blurred face. “Since you’re here anyway, you shall become the foundation of my abyssal power…”

The Chaos Lord didn’t seemed to be worried at all when facing numerous existences of the same rank. A majority of the eyes seemed to be filled with reckless insanity. The Chaos Lord didn’t seem to even care as chaotic origin force sprag forth from the depths of the Abyss, mixing with dark energy as it spread around its giant leg.

“I’ve restricted its actions. I’ll leave the rest to you…” A golden radiance was spreading from Oghma’s body, shrouding the entirety of Azzagrat. Tyr and Tempus brought out their favourite divine weapons, rushing forth towards the Chaos Lord…

……

A terrifying storm swept through the Endless Maze, the constant rain forming a huge turbulent sea.

“Tsk… Why do I have to be paired with you?” The powerful God of Storms looked at the golden orc standing beside him, his face full of disdain.

“I should be the one saying that.” Gruumsh gave Talos a look.

A palace suddenly surfaced within the maze, endless power forming a gigantic evil eye that released a skin-crawling roar: “ZzzzGrrgrgrrr!”

“The ancient Evil Filthy Eye, a Magus who once killed a greater god…” Gruumsh’s eyes lit up as a bright red flag was drawn from his back.

“Only the orcs are the strongest fighters!” he roared, his body expanding in a moment as it clashed with the solid yellow eye.

The aftershocks of the battle caused the entire Abyss to tremble. The demons were intimidated by the formidable power, running about aimlessly as numerous archfiends ruthlessly cursed the gods. They hid within their castles, not daring to come out.

The silhouettes of two powerful archfiends emerged at the edge of the Abyss, one of them the two-brained Demogorgon and the other the King of the Undead, Orcus. Alongside Graz’zt, these were the three Abyssal Lords, the strongest of demons.

“The gods took action according to plan, but it doesn’t seem to be attracting the other Magi…” Orcus frowned. If not for them meddling with the origin force of the Abyss and helping the gods, they wouldn’t at all have been able to infiltrate into the Abyss so quickly, sealing the Chaos Lord and the Evil Filthy Eye where they were.

“…” The Demogorgon’s two heads glanced at each other, surprisingly not arguing. “That’s fine as well. The gods want to use the Abyss as the main battlefield, but the Magi weren’t baited…”

“After the chaos is settled, the Abyss will still be ours…”

“It’s rare for both your heads to reach an agreement. What else should I say?” Orcus’ undead body laughed, the power of death mixing with an aura of chaos to fragment the surrounding space.

“Haha… That’s right, the Abyss shall belong to us demons… Only we can stay here. No one can take it away, not Magi and not gods!” The Demogorgon parroted.

“Let’s kill those gods afterwards!” one of the heads said suddenly.

“No! We shall dominate the Abyss first…” the other retorted, causing Orcus to suddenly shake his head. The unity of these heads seemed to be temporary. The chaos of the Demogorgon would be revealed once more as the threat passed.

‘However, this is indeed a good opportunity…’ A strange light flashed past Orcus’ eyes.

The demons had always coveted the prime material plane and the gods. The Second Dusk would prove to be a great opportunity to attack.

As for their contract with the gods? Since when did chaotic evil have the concept of contracts? With their demonic natures, even the Styx could not hold them to their vows and stop the deaths of their enemies!

Chapter 1194: Battlefield

The two rank 9s were terrifyingly fast. They’d distanced themselves instantly during the explosion, patiently waiting for everything to end.

“What… is… this?” Leylin looked at the confluence of the two worlds, surprise flashing in his eyes. The merged area was devoured under his gaze, reaching a total standstill as the World of Gods and Magus World seemed to reach a perfect balance. They now looked like a dumbbell, the two worlds joined by this point of confluence.

He instantly moved to this new land. Everything here had originally been void, but a black continent had been formed after the blast.

“The laws of space and time have crystallised…” Scanning across the large continent, Leylin found that all kinds of laws had grown stable here, the earth more solid than magic alloy while the space was extremely stable. Even Breaking Dawns would find it difficult to fly here, forget breaking through space.

Leylin used the law of original sin to scan the entire continent, finding out its specific area. It was one tenth the size of the prime material plane, without the slightest hints of life in the rocky desert.

“Where did the Overgod and Magus Will go?” Leylin asked Mother Core who was beside him.

“This place is at the centre of the confluence between the two worlds, having a strange balance…” Mother Core truly was an existence that had survived the Final War. Her insight and abundant experience allowed her to make sense of the situation, “Although the Overgod suffered serious injuries with the destruction of the Weave, the fight between rank 9s exceeds the limit of my comprehension…

“Even if the Overgod is slightly weaker than the Magus WIll, I’m afraid they won’t be able to determine a winner in a short period of time. They should currently be entangled in a dimension we cannot detect, leaving the task of the Final War to the beings of law…”

“You mean…” Leylin looked at the huge continent below them. Although it wasn’t suitable for life, it did indeed serve well as a battlefield for beings of law.

“That’s right… With the two worlds merging together, the devouring has reached a deadlock. The rest depends on the power of the beings of law…”

Mother Core pointed towards the mainland, “This is the final battlefield, a land of nirvana where the losers lose everything. If we can achieve a pivotal victory here, the Magus Will will be able to directly devour the Overgod… However, the opposite is true as well!”

“In other words,” Leylin muttered, “The power of the World Wills are determined by their inhabitants. The victor of this battle here will determine final victory between the two beings of law…”

“Correct. With the two-world plan and our advantage of advancing first, we have a great advantage right now… Don’t squander it!”

“I’m afraid beings of law aren’t enough… We also need large amounts of cannon fodder,” Leylin mused, “We need a regiment of Breaking Dawns led by an existence of laws to take out the lesser and intermediate gods…”

“Our reserves consist of all the Magi across the astral plane. We far exceed the opponent in numbers…”

“We’ll gather our troops, mobilising them for war immediately…” numerous beings of law promised.

Leylin, on the other hand, was staring at the huge black continent. This would be the final battlefield, the land of the end. One could imagine how it would become a terrifying land of death in the near future.

……

On the other end of the battlefield, space trembled as numerous divine kingdoms descended. They formed a strange beehive-like structure, a sort of tight fortress. Numerous prayers sounded out as holy spirits prepared to defend the mainland. The gods had completely disregarded all notions of good and evil, fighting side by side.

Armies of elementals entered the battlefield, accompanied by demon lords led by the two Abyssal Lords. Massive demonic armies rushed forth.

“The divine kingdoms have descended, and all the races allied together… It seems like the gods are staking everything on this too…” Leylin sneered at the opponents’ formation.

“The final battle is nigh… The scale of this war has already exceeded the peak of our past,” Mother Core added.

“It seems so! We should begin with our arrangements too.”

Numerous rules Magus roared. The power of laws fused with each other here, allowing them to unleash their full strength without the World War Armour.

The same held true for the gods. However, such ‘fairness’ wasn’t actually fair.

“Our determination to forge forward… Everything we’ve struggled to obtain from the astral plane shall be displayed here today. The glory of the Magi will shroud everything!” The Magi roared out loud, opening the channels to world after world.

The Dark World, Purgatory, Icy World… A steady stream of troops marched out of every one, their faces flooded with bloodthirst and determination. The weakest was at the Morning Star realm, equivalent to legendaries in the World of Gods. And that was the cannon fodder!

For the sake of the truth, to advance their truesouls, these Magi set off without hesitation. Terrifying war drums echoed throughout the astral plane!

A large ghastly castle revealed itself in Leylin’s assigned area, as if a living snake that released bloodthirsty roars.

““Father!”” Two young Warlocks appeared within the huge hall, and Leylin looked at them with a gentle smile on his face. “I only planned to use my accumulations in Dreamscape and my avatar’s divine kingdom in this Final War. I didn’t think you’d insist on coming, the Ouroboros Clan was too weak to help.“

Standing in front of Leylin were his two oldest sons, Syre and Daniel. Both of them had inherited his bloodline, benefitting from the power of the Nightmare Hydra. They were close to the realm of laws, just like him when he was at the peak of rank 6.

The early stages of advancement for a Warlock depended almost solely on the strength of their bloodline. In this regard, what could exceed the bloodline of the Nightmare Hydra?

“Are you aware of how dangerous the Final War is? Even Breaking Dawns are still cannon fodder here… What do your mothers have to say about this?”Leylin looked at his two oldest sons. They were already a thousand years old, having become ancestral figures of the Ouroboros Clan with children and grandchildren of their own.

“The records of the ancient war in the library described it well enough…” Syre and Daniel looked at each other for a bit, before Daniel stood up and spoke, “We told Mother and Aunt before we left…”

“You…” Leylin sighed. He could see a shadow of his past self in the eyes of his children, holding an insatiable thirst for the truth.

Furthermore, it was difficult for a Breaking Dawn Magus to advance to rank 7. Even Leylin had relied on frantically plundering Dreamscape and the World of Gods to make the leap successfully.

Even though Syre and Daniel had a head start with their bloodlines, they still needed opportunities over a long period of time to bloom. The World of Gods was a shortcut to this. As long as they managed to kill a true god and seize a portion of their godfire or divinity, they would be able to obtain comprehension in laws directly.

None of the Magi in the astral plane could resist this temptation. It was the reason why so many low-ranked Magi had joined despite the shocking casualty rate.

“I respect your choices…” Leylin looked at his sons, traces of gentleness within his eyes. “However… since you have decided on this path, you will have to be prepared to undertake the responsibility of your choices, regardless of the result…”

““Yes sir!”” their excited voices rang out. They hadn’t expected things to go so smoothly…

Leylin clapped his hands once both of them left. Two Lords of Calamity walked into the hall, bowing slightly towards him.

“Follow behind them and protect their lives. I’ll raise your quota for a hundred years in exchange.” The Lords of Calamity were happy with that exchange, and they bowed and retreated.

“The protection of two rank 8s, that shall be it…” Leylin shook his head. These kids couldn’t understand the cruelty of the Final War. Even with the Lords of Calamity protecting them they could lose their lives if they were unlucky enough to meet a greater god or someone of that ilk.

However, Leylin decided not to care about it anymore. He’d given them prior warnings and sent guards. His obligations were fulfilled.

Chapter 1197: A Show

The Magi at Gale Gorge had fallen into chaos with Mother Core and Ignox being ambushed.

The gods launched an attack on them, divine light shining down on the area as angelic holy spirits swarmed the skies, singing praise of their gods as a light of purity razed the Magus castles.

*Hiss!* The void split apart at that moment, revealing the figure of a Nightmare Hydra that covered the skies.

“It’s the Lord of Original Sin!” The Magi rejoiced. On the other side, the petitioners and holy spirits showed fear in their eyes. After all, this existence that had once swallowed the sun was still burning in their memory. That fear was etched deep inside their hearts, and now it had grown into full fledged terror.

“Original Sin!” the Nightmare Hydra hissed, and dense clouds began to envelop the battlefield. Holy spirits, petitioners, even the beings still within the divine kingdoms found their expressions contorting, as the negative emotions in their hearts were magnified over ten million times. Their eyes grew bloodshot.

“Arghhh…” A holy spirit roared, and his body was split into two. A dark beast clawed its way out, possessing the power of hellfire.

“Servants of Original Sin! Attack!” Large numbers were turned in an instant, and the dense army of the divine actually turned around to greet their new Lord. It charged out under the command of the Nightmare Hydra, heading for its original camp.

Cries of anguish rang out, and the magnified emotions were absorbed by a rejoicing Leylin.

“Leylin, Lord of Original Sin!” “Leylin, Lord of Original Sin!” “Leylin, Lord of Original Sin!” A great number of Magi cheered, their voices heard above all other commotions.

The Nightmare Hydra didn’t stop there. The third eye of the devouring head showed itself, looking towards a certain part of the sky.

*Kacha!* The law of devouring broke the void, revealing several flustered gods.

“Stay!” A sharp silver blade flew out of the snake’s jaws, piercing through the middle of a god’s eyebrows.

*Bang!* the god’s eyes were full of shock, turning sluggish as his divine body fell down. Seven Sins had already destroyed his everything, wiping out all chances of his resurrection.

“Lathander!” Several gods seethed in fury, yet they did not tarry as they beat their retreat.

“Lathander? The Morninglord? Becoming a lesser god after the sun was extinguished, what useless trash…” Leylin didn’t feel much joy for killing a former greater god. He instead shifted his glance towards a rank 7 Magus, pulling the man closer, “Where’s Mother Core?”

Even as an existence of laws, the rank 7 felt fear seep through his entire body in the face of the Nightmare Hydra. “T–The Gale Whirlpools,” he stuttered out, “H–Here’s a map, my Lord!”

This old Magus had a cap of spikes on his head, and his beard was now quivering as if the Nightmare Hydra would gobble him up at any second. After all, he was just a rank 7 Magus, and this existence before him had killed a lesser god effortlessly just like that.

“Well done, I’ll leave the remaining tasks to you!” The dark mist covered the map, and the Nightmare Hydra’s figure vanished immediately before the old Magus, entering Gale Gorge. The blades of wind that could repel beings of law couldn’t even create sparks on the Nightmare Hydra’s scales.

“As expected of a peak rank 8 like Leylin Farlier, the most outstanding Magus in the astral plane…” The old Magus muttered, feeling extremely discouraged.

……

“Gale Gorge!” Feeling the ever-growing pressure within Gale Gorge, Leylin sighed.

The valley was littered with azure tornadoes that could swallow up beings of law. The boundless area seemed to contain multiple smaller planes, just like a giant maze. Even powerful beings would get lost here without a map, which Leylin fortunately possessed.

He stepped forth fearlessly, his current strength ensuring that there wasn’t much in the world that could stop him. The Nightmare Hydra bulldozed through the region, crushing many smaller planes into pieces as it created an extremely safe straight path.

“Whirlpool 3, I’m here!” Leylin felt weightless as he jumped into a huge whirlpool. The eye of the storm was devoid of the frightening winds and thick walls that blocked all entry.

“Mother Core and Ignox!” Leylin immediately saw two large figures sealed in thick world crystals, surrounded by numerous gods with auras powerful just standing nearby could cause one to be frightened.

“Chauntea, Tempus, Tyr, and Silvanus…” The Nightmare Hydra howled, spitting out a horrifying amount of destructive power from its nine heads. The gods quickly retreated as it began to shrink, condensing into Leylin’s normal form with Seven Sins in hand.

“Break!” Seven Sins whistled, its sharp blade ramming into the world crystals.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* A web of cracks spread along the surface of the crystals, before they rumbled and exploded. Mother Core’s true body burst out from within, accompanied by Ignox.

“You did well, Leylin!” Mother Core gazed at Leylin in delight. However, her eyes suddenly showed an intense emotion, “NOO!”

Right at the moment they were saved, Ignox’s face was shrouded by a terrifying darkness. A power of distortion formed in his hands, revealing a spear as sharp as could be. The full power of a rank 8 Magus thrust it into Leylin’s chest.

“Eicher’s Thorn!” Mother Core cried out, the majestic power of earth pushing Ignox away as disbelief filled her eyes, “Why? Ignox, why are you doing this?”

“Keke… you’re asking me why I’m doing this?” Ignox laughed maniacally, pulling off his black cloak to reveal the essence of distortion. The rings of power grew more and more terrifying, and his aura eventually shifted into another form.

“Distorted Shadow!” A phantom hydra snarled from behind Leylin, a few of its heads sinking down. His hands filled up with the power of sin as he pulled the dagger out, his eyes on Distorted Shadow, “Was Ignox a clone, or did you use your powers to consume him?”

His words revealed an astounding secret. The rank 7 wizard known as Ignox, always staying within the Magus World, was actually controlled by Distorted Shadow, perhaps even as a clone!

“Is there a difference?” Boundless distorted shadows filled the void as his true body descended. The black rings melded with Distorted Shadow, revealing that the two were of the same essence.

“All I know is that all of you shall fall here…” Fusing back with Ignox, Distorted Shadow became even more difficult to comprehend. He seemed on the verge of reaching peak rank 8 again.

He was initially an incomplete conscient. Even after devouring the God of Murder, Cyric, and making use of his essence to recover, he’d only temporarily regained his status as a peak rank 8. He was still a ways to go from true peak rank 8 power like Mother Core. Now, however, his might exceeded that of Mother Core, closing in on Leylin’s peak prowess.

“Mother Core, and the Lord of Original Sin! The two extreme powers of the Magus World… I see the rise of the stars from your death!” With the four gods present as well, Leylin and Mother Core were heavily surrounded.

*Rumble!* Silvanus’ will descended amidst a green light. The leader of the gods brought with him the power of the four elemental planes.

Wind, earth, water, and fire. The four elemental gods had descended, forming a terrifying seal once more as they broke off all chances of escape!

“Gods!” Mother Core gazed at DIstorted Shadow, seemingly in disbelief. “For the sake of internal conflict you’re actually willing to betray us and side with the gods?”

The fight between Leylin and Distorted Shadow had only been a conflict of interest before. Now, however, Distorted Shadow joining the gods would make him the archenemy of all Magi.

“How can my tolerance and greatness be estimated by you…” Distorted Shadow laughed maniacally, “I will soon become the God of Chaos in the World of Gods, still retaining my powers as a Magus. I am the only one qualified to reach the end of the Final War, obtaining eternity!”

The distortions around Distorted Shadow’s body began to go berserk, representing the agitation in his mind at this moment.

Chapter 1199: Death

“So the hidden thorn was taken care of!” Regardless of what others thought, Leylin was currently in an extremely jovial mood. Having killed Distorted Shadow, he felt like his soul of original sin had grown purer, bringing him closer to the threshold of space and time.

Having devoured three peak rank 8 experts, he’d felt an indiscernible upgrade to his truesoul.

“Everyone else wasn’t injured, and even if Mother Core has to nurse her injuries for a while she did have gains in the gorge…” Leylin rubbed his chin.

Mother Core’s battle was extremely maniacal this time. She’d given her all in order to stop Chauntea from fleeing, suffering severe injuries. It took Leylin’s assistance for her to kill the Earthmother and devour her powers.

This was going to be a great benefit. Once she healed, Mother Core would be a step closer to rank 9, able to try and use the powers of spacetime.

“It’s time,” Leylin sighed and walked out, “Let’s begin the true plan.”

The Underworld of the Gods currently stood opposed to him in the swamp, the vast Styx like a moat that stopped any Magus attacks. However, the Nightmare Hydra roared into the skies like thunder at this moment, charging in without the slightest hesitation whatsoever as it stirred up huge waves. The corrosion and attraction of the Underworld had no power over Leylin.

*Crash!* Leylin broke the defences of the Styx instantly, entering a land very similar to the Underworld.

“Lord of Original Sin!” A greater god surrounded by the laws of death walked out from his palace, shock in his eyes. This was Kelemvor, the opponent Leylin was guarding against.

His shock was not a pretense. Even if the Magi had obtained victory at Gale Gorde, they’d also suffered severe injuries. Rumour had it that Leylin blocked Chauntea’s final attack to protect Mother Core, or both the beings who used the power of the earth would have ended up dead. However, Leylin seemed to be in his peak form here, showing no signs of weakness.

“Die!” The Nightmare Hydra hissed, and a silver light shot out of its vertical eye as it carried the powers of illusion.

“Argh… Don’t dream about it!” Kelemvor tried to put up a final struggle, but a layer of shadow had appeared on his body. This shadow had the same face as Kelemvor, but it was filled with pride and envy, “Hehe… Arrogant God of Death. So you have always been jealous of Jergal’s power and might, and feel like a stray dog that could be left behind at any time?”

This was the influence of Leylin’s powers of emotions. He planted the seed of original sin within Kelemvor’s body, dealing with him like Distorted Shadow dealt with Cyric. He stole a large amount of Kelemvor’s divine force, binding his divine body.

*Boom!* Seven SIns turned into a silver arrow that pierced through Kelemvor’s skull, immediately causing the fall of this greater god. Leylin closed his eyes, feeling his weapon greedily absorb the law of death and nourish him.

Leylin’s powers had long since surpassed Kelemvor’s, and the only reason the god had still been alive was because Leylin was toying with him. Now that he was serious, the Greater God of Death was no match for him!

“Even Seven Sins has Sloth’s Recovery as an ability. Do you think the Lord of Original Sin, someone controlling the law of sloth, would take any time to recover from injuries?” Leylin looked over at where Kelemvor once stood, speaking in a tone of mockery.

However, Kelemvor was already wiped off the face of space and time, losing all traces of his existence. Without the assistance of a rank 9 he could not be resurrected.

*Hiss!* The Nightmare Hydra reared its heads and roared. Lightning, poison, acid, flames… All sorts of matter were spewed from its heads, the only common point being the powerful destructive properties. Kelemvor’s armies were devastated, the land ravaged as his divine palace and his petitioners and holy spirits within taken out.

After everything seemed to return to the beginning of the world, the figure of an ordinary old man dressed in linen appeared in the void. He stood there quietly, not emitting a trace of a powerful aura. The only distinct thing was his eyes, which seemed extremely bright.

“Jergal! I still thought you would help that student of yours!” The Nightmare Hydra shrunk under the mist, turning back into Leylin.

“Even a God of Death must die, such are the laws of the world,” Jergal said in a discerning tone.

Although this god had handed most of his divinity and divine force to Kelemvor in the past, Leylin didn’t dare be complacent in front of him. He sensed that this opponent would be more powerful than the elemental gods.

“You should know my goal by now, right?” Leylin waved his hands, and the powers of original sin sealed the area, creating an illusion that Jergal and Leylin were just staring at each other in confrontation.

“Of course, your search for truth and eternity… Even as a god, I’m influenced by your perseverance…” Jergal smiled gently, “This endless life allowed me to learn more than the rest. The Overgod and Magus Will are currently in the core of the Nirvana Battlefield, locked in battle. The turbulent currents of spacetime there will make it difficult even for existences like us to break in…

“You need my help, Magus.” Jergal looked at Leylin. This primordial God of Death evidently didn’t share the gods’ loyalty towards their World Will. He was instead similar to Leylin, wanting to ascend himself.

“Indeed.” This was Leylin’s purpose in coming here. For the sake of advancing to rank 9, he didn’t mind allying with a god.

“Very well, follow me!” Jergal parted the river with his arms, revealing a path to the core of this battlefield. The purging powers of the Styx had no effect on Leylin’s body of original sin, causing his face to change.

“The core of the Nirvana Battlefield is protected by the ultimate defences of the astral plane. Even having spent so much time, I’ve only managed to open up half the passageway…” The Styx brought the two to an empty void after a long journey. There were no conscients of beings of law here, only wild currents of spacetime with the power to destroy everything. The path of a peak rank 8 was the only way for one to protect themselves.

Leylin could feel two overweeningly powerful conscients in the centre of this void, infinitely close to comprehending the laws of spacetime yet stuck in a deadlock. The World Wills were in an extremely slow process of devouring each other, powered by the inhabitants of their worlds.

“I’m afraid that the victor of this battle will become a true rank 9…” From what Leylin could tell, these two conscients were halfway to rank 9. Only once they devoured their opponents could they break through the threshold, the true meaning of the prophecy of eternity.

“Although we’ll obtain their favour by aiding them, the leftovers from someone else will never compare to what you earn yourself…” Jergal exclaimed, “The combined origin force of the two worlds will definitely be taken by the victor, we won’t have much of a share at all. Eternity will be but a distant dream…”

“What do you want to do?” Leylin asked.

“Ally with me, and we’ll consume the powers of the Magus World and the World of Gods, causing their fight to come to a stalemate. A thousand years, ten thousand years, hundred thousand years, a million years… We will continuously weaken their forces, eventually consuming one of the wills each!”

A crazed expression appeared on Jergal’s face as he spoke of this blatant plan. He didn’t think Leylin had any better options, being the strongest in his own camp at this point. If they joined forces, they could even extend the Final War to a billion years, weakening the World Wills and attempting to devour them as they made for eternity.

“Not a bad plan, and the success rate is extremely high..” Leylin clapped his hands and looked at Jergal. “However, how will two broken worlds with extremely weak wills aid our advancement?”

“You have a better plan?” Wariness surfaced on Jergal’s face. Dense power of death circled around him, many black skeletons arising as his guards.

“These World WIlls are already quite weak! Once we devour them, we’ll be able to advance to rank 9!” Leylin laughed heartily, Seven Sins appearing in his hands.

*Bang!* A black tome of death appeared in Jergal’s hands, its writhing scriptures having recorded the end of all creatures. This was an overgod weapon as well.

“I knew our alliance would rupture eventually, but who knew it would only last this long…” Jergal sighed.

“You think too small, Jergal. Millennia of seclusion has caused you to lose your boldness and your sharp mind.” The Nightmare Hydra behind Leylin fixed its eyes on Jergal, as if staring at delicious prey…

Author’s Afterword

It’s already been a year since last April, and Warlock of the Magus World is finally complete. I’m finally off the pressure of that terrifying release rate, and at the same time I haven’t let down the expectations of the readers; it’s a cause for celebration.

Honestly, this book has achieved far beyond my expectations; we were first in the fantasy ranking last year! This is something only possible because of all the subscriptions, monthly votes, and recommendations; a glory solely belonging to the collective group of readers that have supported me. A thousand thank yous to all of you, and a deep bow!

Thank you to all the friends who’ve subscribed to this novel. Without you, WMW wouldn’t be where it is today. In specific thank you to the three sect masters Lanxi, roseme@ and Empty Mountain New Rain 2015, especially Lanxi for the support of a million fan points. My salute to you!

Thank you also to Myfault, *GGQ*, Silent Seas, Fate is Always Beside Me, Summer Tree⑨, Ultimate Treasure, and Quietly Gently Hehe, thank you for your support and encouragement! There are many others I wish to name for their contributions, but unfortunately, there is a limit to the number of words I have. I regret not being able to list you all.

Thank you to Big Yinyang, Skilful Fishing, Trickling Meander, as well as Single-Horned Sea Cucumber, whose suggestions were extremely incisive. The wealth of information gave me a lot of inspiration.

Finally, I thank the readers of the novel. Your views, recommendations, bookmarking, and subscriptions motivated me through all of this. Thank you!

My knowledge is limited and my writing unskilled; there were times when things were inappropriate and poorly constructed, as well as many other inadequacies in general. I’m extremely sorry for all of it, and thankful for your understanding and forgiveness of those parts.

Lastly, let us meet at my new book, Semi Martial Artist Hero! It’s the legend of a martial artist of infinity, and I look forward to your participation in its writing. Here’s to more recommendations, clicks, and bookmarks O(∩_∩)O~!